Ask not what
your country can do for you.
Ask what you can do
for your country.
Mr. Gorbachev,
tear down this wall!
The only thing we have to fear
is fear itself!
"Uhh, I don't
know what I said. Uhh!"
Erev tov.
My name, Captain Erran Morad.
Today, we learn defense
from radical Islam terror.
Picture the scene.
You are chained to a radiator,
naked with a bag over your head.
All of a sudden, terrorists
break in and kidnap you,
completely ruining
your birthday party.
Yalla.
What we waiting for?
Let's go.
My name Erran Morad.
I was
in the Mossad for--
I mean, I was not
in the Mossad for 13 years.
I here to teach you Krav Maga.
Who are you?
My name
is Jason Spencer.
I'm a state representative
in the Georgia General Assembly.
That's the House
of Representatives.
Jason Spencer, a Republican,
threatened his former
Democratic colleague
after she criticized
his support
of Confederate monuments
on Facebook.
Representative Jason Spencer
says his bill
is definitely in response
to mass terrorists.
House Bill 3
would make it illegal
for people to conceal
their faces in public.
I don't call it
a burka ban.
I call it
an anti-masking statute.
-Okay.
-Okay, because--
-Politically correct.
-Because in the United--
Well, to win
in the legal system,
you cannot-- you cannot
be against the First Amendment.
See, this is how
the Muslims in the country
are using our First Amendment
against them.
You have to fight
fire with fire.
Yeah, so do you know
how to spot the difference
between somebody
who is a terrorist in a burka
and the normal woman
in a burka?
I cannot tell.
-We have developed a technique.
-Mm-hmm.
Do you want to know
how to do this?